Gabriel Matos Marques Silva

Analyst and Systems Developer

PERSONAL PROFILE

I'm a developer with 2 years of working with technology and helping companies to build the best systems, websites, and products. My passion is creating things that matter to people. I am self-taught with a high sense of responsibility. Always looking for new challenges to improve my technical skills and knowledge and also collaborate in the development of the organization as a whole.

SKILLS

- HTML | CSS | SASS | SEO
- JAVASCRIPT | JQUERY | REACT
- BOOTSTRAP | TAILWIND
- TESTES UNITÁRIOS (JEST)
- GIT
- SQL
- SCRUM
- LINUX
- WORDPRESS

EDUCATION

Analysis and Systems Development | 2017-2020

FATEC - Technology College

LANGUAGES

Portuguese Fluent
English Advanced

CONTACT

Phone: +55 (12) 99703-4468 E-mail: gaabrielmatoss@gmail.com

Website: gabrielmatos.tech

linkedin: linkedin.com/in/gaamatoss/ Location: São José dos Campos - SP

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Developer | FULLTIME

AGROTOOLS | JAN 2023 - Present

- Front-end Development (Javascript, Vue, Jquery)
- Back-end Development (C#, Javascript, SQL)

Analyst / Software Developer | FULLTIME SONDA IT | JAN 2021 - DEZ 2022

- Front-end Development (Javascript, React, Angular)
- Back-end Development (Java, Node)
- Maintenance Applications (Java, Javascript, SQL)
- Generate reports (SQL)
- Infrastructure Maintenance (JBOSS)
- SAP MM Queries

Analyst / Software Developer | TRAINEE

SONDA IT | OUT 2019 - DEZ 2020

- Maintenance Applications (Java, Javascript, SQL)
- Generate reports (SQL)
- Infrastructure Maintenance (JBOSS)
- SAP MM Queries

Wordpress Developer (Freelance)

Panela Aberta - SET 2020

• Website made for a UNIFESP extension group in nutrition course using WordPress.

(https://panelaaberta.unifesp.br/sobre)

Councilor website - OUT 2020

 Website made for a councilor in the city of São José dos Campos using WordPress.

PROJECTS

Libras Detection - TCC (06/2020 - 06/2021)

• Platform to help children with hearing impairment to become literate using an artificial intelligence capable of recognizing LIBRAS (Brazilian Sign Language) gestures. Project developed using javascript, React.js, and Tensorflow.js to do the recognitions. (https://github.com/gaamatoss/LibrasDetection)